

## Illia Rachkovan

# **QA** Engineer

Linked In - linkedin.com/in/illia-rachkovan-7a54101a2

Email – iliarachkovan@gmail.com

**GitHub** - https://github.com/IliaRachkovan/Portfolio-Illia-Rachkovan-QA-QC-Manual.git

**Mobile - 0938164796** 

# **Summary**

I Have a good understanding of quality control (QC), quality assurance (QA) processes, requirements, methodology, testing types/approaches and more. I possess experience in testing web, mobile and desktop applications, Database, API. I also experienced in creating test documentation such as: test cases, checklists, test plans, bug reports. I have strong communication and organization skills, positive, responsible and flexible person.

#### **Technical skills**

#### **Databases**

My SQL

# **Tools and Technologies**

- HTML/CSS
- Technical documentation/ SRS
- XML, JSON
- REST API
- Postman
- Fiddler Classic, Fiddler everywhere
- Jira, Mantis
- Git
- TestRail
- Jmeter

# Methodologies

• Agile, SCRUM, Kanban, Waterfall

# **Experience**

Company: Adidas

**Position:** Store manager

**Responsibilities:** Management

- Organizing all stores processes
- Execution of sales plans by the store
- Monitoring and influence on KPI affecting the company's sales

- Interviewing and hiring employees
- Teaching and motivating team
- Tracking employees' KPIs
- Cash operations
- Meeting with management team to discuss situation in stores and share best practices
- Implementing of visual merchandising recommendations

**Duration:** 2020 – 2022 (2 years)

**Achievements:** I consider my main achievement to be taking on the challenge of opening a new store for the company I worked for.

In preparation for the opening, I conducted interviews, hired and trained reliable employees who had worked with me for at least one year. I also organized the process of preparing the goods and the visual part of the store in a timely manner.

All the work was completed on time.

After the opening, I organized the store's work and the achievement of business goals.

Company: Adidas

Position: Service consultant, administrator

**Responsibilities:** 

- Working with customers
- Improving store KPI's
- Teaching fellow workers

**Duration:** 2014 – 2020 (6 years)

## **Education**

- GlobalLogic QA Manual course 2023
- QATestLab online course 2021
- Masters in Electromechanical automation systems and electrical drive

Admiral Makarov National University of Shipbuilding

2013-2017

# Language

• English – Intermediate B2